# LuisGomes Software Developer

Software Developer with over 13 years of experience working with international teams, involved in the whole life cycle of different projects, from requirement analysis to their delivery. Comfortable working with several different technologies and programming languages, especially on Linux. Great at solving problems, and helping other people with their own challenges.

#### **Contact Me**

## +351 916 289 470

- lmagomes@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/lmagomes/
- github.com/lmagomes/cv

### My Skills



### Experience

### Software developer Q-Free

April 2006 - Present

Currently leading a team in an agile environment for the implementation of new features, as well as the maintenance of current features. This includes meeting and working closely with the customer for gathering requirements, and demonstrating functionality during development.

Main technologies: Java, React, Javascript, Python, Jenkins, Linux.

Automated collection and storage on a data warehouse, of data used for SLA and KPIs calculations. This was a previously manual task, and freed up the teams time while also allowing for easier exploration of the system data.

Main technologies: Python, Pandas, apache airflow, PostgreSQL, Linux.

implementation of an operational back-office for Ascendi's roadway tolling concessions. Part of the team responsible for gathering requirements, writing Specifications, implementing the solution, and presenting and performing the acceptance tests for the finalized solution on the customer's premises.

Main technologies: SAP ASE, T-SQL, C#, WCF, Linux, Windows.

Started working in Q-Free developing interfaces for Q-Free's hardware, used by different projects in Via Verde Portugal.

Main technologies: C, Linux.

### Software developer Intern Sybase Portugal

February 2005 - August 2005

Worked on the maintenance of several internal applications helping with the implementation of new features and bug fixes.

### My Languages

### English

Professional proficiency.

Portuguese

Native

#### **Education**

Business Intelligence post graduation Universidade Católica Portuguesa

2012-2013

Computer Science Universidade Lusófona

2000-2006